Barbara Marrero

1S159 Dillon Lane, Villa Park, IL 60181 | 630-640-0253 | audilady74@yahoo.com

Summary of Qualifications

Bi-lingual (Spanish/English) Banking Professional with over 15 years extensive experience in servicing elite corporate banking clients in the Treasury products space, seeking an opportunity to leverage my customer service, analytical and problem resolution skills.

Core Competencies

Fluent in Spanish Analytical Collections
Banking / Finance Team Player Documentation
Customer Service Sales Organizational Skills

Fraud Mitigation Networking Compliance

Experience

CLIENT SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE | BMO HARRIS BANK | 2013 TO PRESENT

- Demonstrating an in-depth understanding of Treasury Management product and service capabilities to our corporate banking clients.
- Analyzing and interpreting service problems to identify root causes and recommendations as distinct from symptoms.
- During conversation and analysis, exploring and identifying enhancement and cross-sell opportunities and bringing these opportunities to the appropriate sales professional.
- Uncovered fraudulent transactions avoiding millions of dollars in potential losses to the bank. Example: worked with the client, the bank wire room team and the receiving bank to block the deposit of funds into a fraudulent vendor account saving the bank \$497,000.
- · Identified account vulnerabilities to fraud, identified bank product and upsold solutions.
- · Surpassed standards for calls answered and emails responded to.
- · Won "Beam" recognition for empathetic listening, problem resolution skills and customer satisfaction.
- · Won the "Bear of the year award, exemplifying outstanding team work and interpersonal skills.
- Knowledgeable in a variety of commercial and treasury products; Automated Clearing House, Domestic and International Writing Instructions, Lockbox (Wholesale and retail), Positive Pay, EDI files, transmission methods.

PORTFOLIO MANAGER | BMO HARRIS BANK | 2005-2013

- · Gold and Silver level elite client management for the bank.
- · Primary point of contact for the successful commercial banking clientele with high service expectations.
- Responded to client concerns in a professional manner that conveys ownership, competence, respect and the value of the client relationship.

- Took timely action, either personally or by referral, to close the gap between what client expects and what they are experiencing in the performance of the bank and its products.
- · Tracking collection of client service fees.
- · Prioritized multiple assignments from clients and coworkers, completing with minimal supervision.
- · Experienced in working closely with bank partners in different areas of the organization.
- · Consistently received excellent annual reviews and commensurate performance-based raises.
- Thorough investigation and troubleshooting of client issues, ensuring a high level of client satisfaction.
- Recognized on multiple occasions for going "above and beyond" for premier clients. Example: One client sent a box of Shari's Berries for us retrieving a fraudulent wire for \$100,000 after an email was hacked. On another occasion an LA based ethnic foods company sent my department 100 lbs. of food (Burritos, Enchilada's and dessert tacos).

Computer and Banking System Skills

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook), Livelink, Document Direct, Alltel, Pep+

Education

MASTERS OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION | 2003 - 2005 | BENEDICTINE UNIVERSITY

· Graduated with a 3.94 GPA

BACHELORS OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION | 1999-2001 | ROBERT MORRIS UNIVERSITY

- Major: Marketing
- · Graduated Magna Cum Laude